What are you afraid of? It's only rock & roll.
Trick or Treat is a horror, comedy, music film directed by Charles Martin Smith.
Eddie Weinbauer, a metalhead teen who is bullied at school, looks to his
heavy metal superstar idol, Sammi Curr, for guidance.
When Curr is killed in a hotel fire, Eddie becomes the recipient of the only copy of Curr's
unreleased album, which, when played backwards, brings Sammi back to life.
As Halloween approaches, Eddie begins to realize that this
isn't only rock 'n roll...it's life and death.
Eddie Weinbauer, played by Marc Price.
Sammi Curr, played by Tony Fields.
Leslie Graham, played by Lisa Orgolini.
Tim Hainey, played by Doug Savant.
Angie Weinbauer, played by Elaine Joyce.
Roger Mockus, played by Glen Morgan.
Trick or Treat is a 1986 American supernatural horror film  directed by Charles Martin Smith in his
directorial debut, and produced and released by De Laurentiis Entertainment Group.
It stars Marc Price and Tony Fields, with special appearances by
Gene Simmons and Ozzy Osbourne in his film debut.
The plot centers on an outcast metalhead teenager who is
haunted by the ghost of his rock hero.
It was released on October 24, 1986.
Despite receiving initially middling reviews, Trick or
Treat has developed a cult following.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, rock star, halloween, heavy metal.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.